brunchnews.com 2014-05-15

# Privacy Policy | BrunchNews.com

BrunchNews.com knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared. This Privacy Policy explains what information of yours will be collected by _BrunchNews_ when you use the _BrunchNews.com_ and how _BrunchNews.com_ will use the information. Additionally, it explains how you can control the collection, correction and/or deletion of such information. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information we collect by other means (including offline) or from other sources. Capitalized terms that are not defined in this policy are defined in our Terms of Use. Our expectation is that Users will use this service for harmless social purposes. 

### What Information Is Collected?

BrunchNews.com will store the information that you provide to us during the registration process (if any) as well as during the use of the Service. This information may include but is not limited to your email address, name, picture, phone number, and/ or Facebook/Twitter ids as well as non identifying information like gender, Birthday etc. While using the service, you may choose to share more information such as comments/Views. 

BrunchNews.com also finds your IP address, Operating System, Browser Type, the address of the referring site and your activity on BrunchNews.com for improving the content of the service, customizing the advertising on the Service and communicating with you about our services.

We may also automatically collect certain information through the use of "cookies". These are small files that your browser places on your computer. We may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with our services, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on our services, and to improve our services. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit.

### How Is My Information Protected?

_BrunchNews.com_ uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. However, BrunchNews.com cannot guarantee the security of user account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of user information at any time.

Your BrunchNews.com account's personal information (if any collected) is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You can prevent unauthorized access to your account and personal information by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your computer and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account. 

### How Is My Information Shared?

### Sharing with friends

Your activity on BrunchNews.com will be shared with your friends when you have connected and identified your Facebook and twitter Profiles. 

### Sharing with everyone

Information such as your name and picture, social network links, comments/Views will be shared with the BrunchNews.com community at large. 

### Sharing with partners and authorities

We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that it is necessary in order to comply with the law of the land, to enforce our terms of use or to protect the rights, property, or safety of _BrunchNews.com_ , our employees, our users, or others. 

### Your Choices About Your Information

You have the right to decline to submit personally identifiable information on our Service. If you choose to do so, BrunchNews.com may not be able to provide certain services to you. You may update or correct your account information [and email preferences] at any time by logging in to your account (If created). 

### How Is Information Removed From My Account?

Even after you remove information from your account or profile, copies of that information may remain viewable elsewhere, to the extent it has been shared with others, it was otherwise distributed pursuant to your privacy settings, or it was copied or stored by other users.

### Tracking

_BrunchNews.com_ uses Google Analytics to better understand who is using the Service, and how it is being used. Google Analytics uses cookies to collect and store anonymous information such as the time(s) of visit, pages visited, time spent on each page of the website, IP address, and type of operating system used. We use this information to improve the Service and make it appealing to as many users as possible.

### Links

You may come across links to external websites on BrunchNews.com. We are not responsible for the practices employed by these websites. This privacy policy governs only the practices of our service.

### Will There Be Changes To This Privacy Policy? 

BrunchNews.com may amend this Privacy Policy periodically. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make material changes in the way we use Personal Information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our _Service._ Users are bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when they use the Service after such changes have been first posted.

### What If I Have Questions Or Concerns? 

If you have any questions or concerns regarding your privacy while using the Service, please send a detailed message 

to: [contactus{@}brunchnews.com](mailto:contactus@brunchnews.com) We will make every effort to resolve your concerns.
